Maybe. Still said worse.
He's around
They went to the Cascale, you know, you gotta get them in, apparently.
They went to the composer and said,
can you create a score which is just thrashing pounding waves of sonic noise
with no malady to it and make it really overpowering so that you feel fatigued
after only watching the trailer so that was the brief they gave to the
They delivered.
They absolutely did.
We will face this together.
For our life.
We will fight it together, as a family.
I have that on you.
Mean I feel like they're they're going for all the like tried and tested stuff
You know family team of disparate heroes having to learn to work together to combat an existential threat all the stuff
this worked for the past 20 years of like superhero movies. They're deploying it here.
I literally have that action figure that they just showed.
Yeah, like they just put a different costume on the damn thing
Also, you said for the past 20 years, I mean, has it like, well, maybe up until about maybe
2017 I mean I would agree to go as far as 1920 even maybe there's us to fall
apart then yeah but then easily it's because they've tried to thank so much
other extraneous stuff onto it, but I think if you were to drill it down to like that more
or classical message of like a family,
an actual family of people, like trying to work together
with people in fairly well-carved-out roles.
That could work.
Yeah, well I mean, you know, I don't disagree with you, there's pieces here that could be
part of a great film but it's just I just don't trust them anymore at all. No, no, I think you're
right not to I think you're right not to but if I was to put my my money on any
any Marvel project this year, it would be this.
It would be Thunderballs.
with. Thunderbolts has this advantage of no one cares about it and no one really knows
much about the characters so what they can do if they play around with them it
It doesn't matter as much.
That's what they said about that beetle.
Yeah, but that wasn't Marvel. So I just think with Thunderbolts like there's there's not enough interest either way
So even if it's good people won't care enough to go watch it. So they're probably gonna flop nowhere. What do you yeah?
I have a feeling thunderbolts will be like actually pretty good and no one will see it anyway. I I have that
It's such an irrelevant property that there's a possibility that they might do some cool
shit with it and then no one will even notice because no one will go to see it.
That's just how I'm thinking.
Okay.
Okay, they can play around with it. They can literally do whatever they want
No one cares about any of the characters except for Bucky.
Like, none of those characters anybody gives a shit about.
So they can do whatever they want.
And one of the best part about that theory is if I'm wrong, no one will notice anyway.
Dude, it's sort of like no one cares.
and that's a curvy space it just seems a little kind of weirdly stretched and smooth it just
which seems like one or two years away from getting a ticket, you know, invited into space.
Well, it's because she's pushing for it.
Like the story for brave astronauts head up into space
I
I come back forever changed.
so yeah she's she's probably older than she should be well yeah she's like 39
Right.
Yeah.
I think the characters meant to be like mid-twenties, as I am.
So right.
Yeah, they should definitely a Pedro Pascal's what like 50. I don't know he's well
He was like in his 20s, so I don't know but they definitely should have went with a younger fantastic for in my opinion
Yeah.
I don't know, we'll see.
It has to be us.
all this stuff is just like i don't know man like it would have been super impressive 20 years ago
but it's like I've seen it all so many times before. It's got a good visual aesthetic to it.
I think it kind of has balance in everything. It looks pretty good.
They're going for the very Clinton 1960s look, which is fair.
That's when Fantastic Four started.
We will protect you.
Okay
Yeah, it still happened.
I don't know. That's...
I feel like because that's the thing about Galactus is size you get you get one shot to sort of
really make it imposing. Have it and walk like, you know, a smaller Godzilla. It's just a bit like
And so if I was to ask you guys, right, what are you more excited for this or Superman?
Marvel are gonna have everything invested in Avengers right they'll be
like oh god we need that to work DC on the other hand everyone's gonna be
fucking running around in circles if Superman fails and James Gunn will be a
part of like a meeting every hour for the next few weeks if it fails oh yeah
And just before I fuck off, here's a little reminder that the Kickstarter for Trial by Fire still has a couple of weeks left for donations.
We already reached our funding goal within the first few days.
So big thanks to everyone who donated, and we're now pushing towards our stretch goals to try to produce more and better quality short films.
So if you're feeling generous and you'd like to support independent filmmakers, not to
mention take a shot at having your own idea turned into a short movie then
and consider heading to the Kickstarter page
the description and having a look. Anyway, that's all I've got for today. Go away now.
burgerotic.com
Decades come and go but entertainment is forever or so they thought all the wood used to be where dreams come true
but now it's where dreams go to die welcome to neurotic and this is the top
five murder franchises.
Yeah, tickets are wearing it!
It's going to be a bumpy ride!
For this list we're going to go over the top 5 blockbuster genre franchises, in most cases
that brought generations of fans together, of all makes, shapes and sizes.
Franchises that have been vandalized.
Suffering and perverted by corporate culture and a never-ending quest to turn art into content.
This wasn't an easy list to put together, but we broke it down to this.
what franchise committed the worst crimes against imagination and we start with number
5. The Terminator.
Come with me if you want to live.
Some may argue that the Terminator was never a franchise and only a vehicle for Arnold Schwarzenegger
written by James Cameron for two films
And you may be right after two groundbreaking films